Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Good morning, Mr. Pouty-Pants!
Commander Sorbet.
What now?
It's Planet 448, sir.
The native uprising
has gotten worse.
We can't keep them
down for much longer.
Fine.
Then send more soldiers.
That's the trouble, sir.
With all the fighting
on other worlds,
we barely have any to spare.
What?
Damn it.
Disengage. Disengage!
This is Sorbet. Report.
Have you tracked
down the remaining
Namekian survivors yet?
I'm sorry, Commander.
We've deployed a small
army of spy drones,
but they haven't
turned up anything.
We still can't find them.
Well then. There's no choice,
we'll go to Earth.
Planet Earth? But isn't that
a bit too dangerous, sir?
I know they
have Dragon Balls
and that female
knows how to find them,
but she's in league
with the Super Saiyan!
Without the Namekians,
what else can we do?
Earth is a risk
we have to take.
Besides, I have
no intention of
involving that human woman.
Our spy drones may have
failed in other systems,
but they've
helped on Earth.
According to their data,
she's not the only one
capable of finding
Dragon Balls.
Tagoma! The two of us
are going to Earth.
Sir! But why not send out
a larger unit, sir?
It seems the
Earth Saiyans can detect
substantial power levels
without using a Scouter.
Obviously, more troops means a
bigger risk of being noticed.
Understood, sir.
We'll get the job done.
But Commander,
are you sure you want to
go down there yourself?
Of course I'm sure.
Lord Frieza is
coming back to life.
Commander Sorbet,
look! I've found them.
Excellent!
Looks like they've
already gathered six of them.
Then what are you
waiting for? Let's move!
We have to catch them
before they've got them all!
Yes, sir!
Don't disappoint me.
You said the last one was here.
Uh. That's right.
The ball should be
directly below this spot.
Of course, that's
where it gets tricky.
The ocean floor's
really deep here
so we'll need some kind
of submersible.
Tagoma,
dive down and retrieve it.
Right!
We'll, uh, be over here.
Mai! This is your
fault for not moving
quick enough
with the Dragon Radar!
Now these crazy alien jerks
are gonna snatch 'em all up
and steal the wishes
that should be ours!
You're the one who
said we cooperate,
you should've
just told 'em "no"!
Here's what we're
gonna do now.
You're gonna take your gun,
and you're gonna whip out
that pretty little sword.
Then chop-chop-chop-
pow-pow-pow
and they're finished!
Wait, if we're trying to beat 'em
then shouldn't you attack too?
I'm supposed to be
the brains of this operation!
But very well. Let's roll!
Aah!
Just because
I'm small doesn't mean
you should take
me lightly, Earthlings.
Aah!
Hey sorry, we didn't mean
to get back home so late.
Hi, little Pan!
Oh, sorry Mommy
wasn't here sooner!
Unkie Piccolo's
green face must've been
really scary, huh?
Hmm...
Huh? You look worried,
what's wrong?
I'm sensing some bad
energy in that direction.
Huh. I do too,
now that you mention it.
But, what could it be?
I don't know.
Aw, you're okay, sweetie.
You're okay.
Mommy's right here.
All right,
get on with it.
Look. After we do this,
are you the kind of guy
who's gonna kill us?
Don't you worry, Earthling.
There's a chance we may
have use for you later,
so it's in our best
interest to keep you alive.
Now go on.
Or don't you trust me?
Eeh. Sort of?
Hey. I have a
boyfriend named Trunks,
and if anything
happens to me,
he'll make you regret it!
I'm not going to
tell you again!
Eternal dragon, Shenron!
By your name I summon you!
It just got dark.
Could it be?
Yes. It's definitely Shenron.
I am the dragon, Shenron.
I shall grant you
any wish. Now speak!
He's all yours.
Go on, Commander.
This is our chance.
All right.
Let's just hope this works.
I wish for Frieza!
Bring him back to life!
What? A-Are you deaf?
You told us I could
wish for anything, right?
Of course, it can be done.
But his body was cut to pieces
and obliterated many years ago,
and I cannot restore it.
There is little point in
returning his soul to that form.
He's still in pieces, huh?
Well great. That sucks.
But think about it. With the
new regeneration machines
we use for our troops,
this may not be a problem.
Even if the damage is severe,
we should still be
able to repair him.
Of course.
That should work.
Hey! I don't care
what shape he's in,
just bring him back
like I told you!
It's unwise to be
rude to a dragon.
Eh. Sorry. Pretty please
bring Frieza back to life.
That better?
A foolish choice, but very well.
Hm.
Ah!
It's his eyeball!
Granted. Now what
is your second wish?
What? A second wish?
I didn't know I get two?
Indeed. When Earth's
Guardian was replaced,
my powers were altered as well.
A second?
What should it be?
I could wish to bring
King Cold back to life too.
Then we'd be
really unstoppable.
We wish
for a million zeni!
Hmm?!
Your wishes
have been fulfilled.
I bid you farewell.
Agh.. you'll pay for that!
Commander, wait!
There's no time for that!
The Saiyans may know
we're here now.
We have to move quickly!
Agh! Okay, fine. Get off me!
I know we packed a
cryo-preservation device
on the ship. We always do!
Don't just stand there, get it!
Yes, sir!
Augh!
This is
Lord Frieza, after all.
His strength, our tech?
I'm positive we can
put him back in one piece!
Um, excuse me, guys?
You're, uh,
forgetting something.
I think
you might need it.
Eh-uh!
Yes, good work, Earthling.
We'll remember you if we
come back to this planet.
But next time
we'll have Lord Frieza
and our soldiers, too.
Way to think on
your feet, Shou!
Then you could've asked for more,
like a hundred million zeni.
That would've been, you know,
a hundred times better.
Uh. I just thought,
this was enough.
If you're too rich
you're kids turn out to be
jerks who own night clubs.
Uuh... Yeah! You're right!
Now who wants
Mongolian barbecue?
- Yay! I'm starving!
- I want pudding too!
I'm getting
a whole table of it!
It's gone now.
Wonder what that was about.
Something tells me
we're in trouble.
Ah... Welcome back,
Lord Frieza.
It's great to see you.
And you are?
Uh. My name's
Sorbet, my lord.
I was part of your
support staff before...
in the Third Stellar Region?
Oh. You do
look vaguely familiar.
Actually. I've been
leading your forces, my lord.
Just in your
absence, of course.
You've been in charge?
Hm...
Seems I've actually been
brought back to the living world.
Yes, Using Dragon Balls and
our new regeneration machine.
Dragon Balls, you say? Ah.
Right, those orbs from
that miserable planet.
The fact is we couldn't
find the Namekian survivors.
So Tagoma and I risked
our lives going to Earth.
We used the Dragon
Balls there, instead.
Yes it's like
he said, my lord.
I'm Tagoma and it was
my great honor to play
such a vital role
in bringing you back.
While I, Sisami,
managed the fleet.
And these two have both been
outstanding warriors
under my command, sir,
rivaling even Zarbon
and Dodoria at their peaks!
Hm. It sounds like
you've done well, men.
But tell me, is it just hard to count
the days when you're dead,
or did it take you a long
time to restore my life?
Ah... I'm sorry,
Your Lordship.
Between hunting down the
Dragon Balls and developing
the regeneration technology,
it wasn't easy.
Oh, I'll tell you
what isn't easy.
Suffering for all of
those years in Earth's Hell!
You must be relieved then!
We're so glad you're back!
Hm! I bet my empire's
been falling to pieces
without me here
cracking the whip.
And you only revived me
because you were desperate.
No, sir!
That's not it, I swear!
It just took us a lot
longer than we hoped.
But on the bright side, it gave
us time to improve our tech!
We've restored
you completely,
without any cyborg support!
Then, my father?
Our plan was to bring
you back first, Lord Frieza,
and then King Cold, as soon
as we could make another wish.
Hm! No, I don't
think we need to
- worry about reviving him.
- Huh?
Father was bloated
with self-importance.
Yes. Of course.
Whatever you think
is best, my lord.
Ah-ahh!
Just as I suspected,
my skills have grown
a bit rusty around the edges.
It seems I may need
to wait a tad longer
before exacting
my sweet revenge.
Uh... your revenge, sir?
Don't tell me
you're surprised.
Of course my vengeance
must be satisfied!
I won't rest until both those
Super Simians are vanquished!
They'll pay for
what they did to me
and they'll pay in blood!
Forgive me if I'm
speaking out of turn.
But wouldn't it be
wiser to forget about
the Saiyans, my lord?
And focus on the
rest of the Universe?
Aah!
Commander Sorbet, help me!
Tagoma!
Shields!
Raise the shields!
Either you brought
the most cowardly of my troops
to my welcoming party,
or the Frieza Force
has become woefully
faint of heart.
How do you expect us to
run an Empire that strikes
fear across the galaxies
while we're cowering from
a handful of Saiyan garbage?
But--But sir.
That Saiyan, Goku,
has gone through
a great deal
while you were gone.
He's faced all sorts
of foes and prevailed.
What are you telling me?
He's more formidable now
than when he bested me?
Uh... Yes, sir.
I know that's hard to hear,
but it's the truth.
I'd expect nothing less
from that monkey.
I'll just have to
become stronger myself.
It's as simple as that.
But my lord,
he even beat Majin Buu!
That's the last battle
our drones recorded.
Who knows if there were more!
Father once said there were
two warriors in the Universe
I was never to challenge.
Beerus the Destroyer
and Majin Buu.
You're telling me
Goku beat that Buu?
Uh... Yes sir.
Then he's even
mightier than I dared to dream.
This could be
most salubrious for me.
Uh. I'm not sure
I know that word, sir.
It means beneficial to a
person's health and well-being.
And what could be more
salubrious for a conqueror
than the motivation
to become so strong
he's never dethroned again?
Um, as you say, my lord.
I've never trained
a day in my life.
There was never a need.
Imagine what could happen if
I unlock my latent potential.
Hold on. You mean,
you could get stronger?
Stronger than your final form?
Of course, my minion.
Now shut your gaping mouth
so I can concentrate.
If I train in earnest
for the next four months...
Yes. I could reach
a power level of
one-point-three million.
Look, I already told you!
I am a super-elite
galactic patrolman!
Now go and
get Bulma for me!
And like I keep telling you,
Bulma won't take visitors
without an appointment!
You foolish human!
Do you have any idea how far
I've come to tell her
the Earth is in danger!
Oh, Taco,
long time no see!
Not Taco, Jaco!
Well, either way,
it's been a long time.
So what do ya say, Paco?
How 'bout I show you
my beautiful goldfish?
A fish made of gold?
Wow, those eyes are
more like what you see
in an Erukan bull frog.
That's because these
are pop-eyed goldfish.
Pretty cute, huh?
Whoa...
Hey!
Hold on! I don't
have time for this!
Oh. Right.
Oh, wow, it really is Jaco!
Long time no see, space cop.
What brings you
down to our planet?
I had an interesting talk
with your sister, Tights.
She tells me you're
buddies with the man who
defeated Frieza. Is that true?
Huh? Well, I guess,
technically there are
two people
who've beaten Frieza.
The first, of course,
was my teenage son, Trunks.
And the other person was
our old family friend, Goku.
Your son?
Granted I hadn't given
birth to him at that point
'cause he came from the
future in a time machine.
Right now he's
a cute little boy.
The future? You tell me
that like it's no big deal!
Galactic law specifically
states altering time
is a serious felony!
Well then those laws
are clearly stupid.
Look, let's not
get sidetracked.
The reason I'm really here
is to see this friend of yours
who's beaten Frieza. I have
grave news to tell him!
Yeah, that's not
happening today, Jaco.
Right now he and my husband
are on some planet
doing who knows what
with Lord Beerus.
Lord Beerus?
Oh, come on. You're in
the Galactic Patrol
and you don't know Beerus?
Lord Beerus the Destroyer!
They're friends
with Lord Beerus?
That's impossible!
You can't be friends with
someone who doesn't
actually exist!
Think that if you want,
but it's your funeral.
I don't have time to debate
cosmic theology with you!
Frieza's been resurrected and is
on his way to Earth as we speak!
He's got a thousand men!
Huh? He's alive again?
The same Frieza who put me
through all of that trouble
back on Planet Namek?
Though I never
actually met the guy...
I'm not sure
what he looked like.
I did a quick sketch.
Okay, that's not
what I was picturing.
But seriously,
he couldn't be back!
Right?
Wrong.
And with a
thousand soldiers?
At least.
And now that I've
told you, I'm outta here.
Because I'm young and smart
and do not feel like dying.
Well, good luck guys.
You could've
told us that first,
instead of playing
with goldfish!
Hey! Wait! Come back, Jaco!
Wait, Frieza's back?
Oh, Whis! Hello!
Where are you, Whis?!
I've got a strawberry
sundae right here!
If you want it, you better
come down and eat it,
before the sun melts it!
It's a hot day today!
Dessert, really?! I just
told you Frieza's back!
Trust me, this is the best
way to get his attention.
I need details. How long
'til Frieza gets here?
Hmm. I'd say in
about an hour or so.
You jerk!
Why didn't you say that?!
Now I have no time to
warn anyone who could help!
So rude.
Come on! Let's go!
We did it! We're as
rich as rich guys!
Can't wait to
spend this loot!
Hey, watch it, lardo!
Please don't.
Crap, they're coming for us!
I'm gonna floor it. Hold on!
Smoke 'em, boss!
This pig thinks he
can keep up with me?
Well, suck on this!
Awe yeah!
Hey, what the hell?!
Yeah, that was dangerous!
You think that was dangerous?
Are you kidding me?
You just robbed a bank!
Ooh...
Come on, guys.
Stop stealing stuff.
You're better than this.
We'll never
do it again! Please!
We're sorry.
We play too many video games!
Don't tell my mom!
Huh?
What?
Why's Bulma calling?
You're go for Krillin.
Oh, sorry Bulma,
but you got bad timing.
Yeah, I'm in
the middle of a bust.
What? Frieza?
That's impossible.
Right. Right. I'm on it, okay!
I'm headed out right now.
I'll find Master Roshi and get
him up to speed, don't worry.
Okay. I'll see ya soon.
Frieza, he's...
He's come back to life?
I should be going too.
Don't get your feelings hurt
but I'm still a lot
stronger than you are.
Maybe, but it's more
important that you stay here
and take care of
our little Marron.
But actually,
there is one more way
you can help the cause.
I think I should go old school!
So Goku and Vegeta
aren't even here right now?
They're on some other
world with that cat?
Yeah I'm afraid they are.
We just have to hope
they get our message soon
so they can join the fight.
At least we still have
Buu and Gohan around, though.
They can buy us some time!
Well, see ya, babe!
He's so cool.
We'll be arriving
at Earth shortly, my lord.
You're telling me
you've had a decade
and the most advanced
fleet of all time,
yet you only found one of
the Saiyans who killed me?
Yes, believe me, sir.
We started hunting for
the other one the moment
after you passed on.
But no matter where
in the Universe we looked,
we couldn't find him.
It's possible he simply retired
to some backwoods world,
or maybe even died.
We're confident the
only two Saiyans on Earth
are Goku and Vegeta.
Unless you count their
half-breed offspring,
one of which is fully grown.
Fine. We'll start there.
But Lord Frieza,
once you get revenge,
what's to stop someone
from using the Dragon Balls
to bring the Super Saiyan
back to life all over again?
Ha! A worthy concern.
That's why I'll destroy the
Earth while destroying him.
Then the Dragon Balls,
as well as that Hell,
will be permanently expunged.
I see, my lord.
That reminds me, do you
remember our contingency
in case things
don't go as planned?
Yes, of course.
I'll be ready.
Good. Let's go.
Oh. I love spring.
Quit your daydreaming!
Damn it!
He's just mocking us!
Huh?
Really, Kakarot?
Even now you've gotta
get a shot in at me?
Relax, Vegeta! That was
an honest mistake!
Oh, my. Such bickering.
Ugh! Kakarot,
just stay outta my way.
It's time I got
Whis all to myself!
What? Vegeta, wait!
Down you go.
Huh?
Hm.
Easy now.
I-I can't move.
Aah!
Haaa!
Who's got
the upper hand now?
Okay, boys, I think
we're done for now.
I'm quite disappointed.
Neither of you yet possess
the necessary speed.
Look. I even signed
both your tops!
What?
When did you do that?
You two are still
thinking before you move,
rather than just moving.
I'm afraid this habit
is especially strong
with you, Vegeta.
This overthinking is
limiting your fighting speed.
Messages can
only travel through
your nervous system so fast.
When you rely on thoughts
for physical action
you lose precious fighting time.
You really do like to
overthink everything, Vegeta.
Oh, shut your face!
You're only thinking less
because you're an idiot!
Your end goal should be
to master the ability
to have each part of
your body think and move
independently
of the other parts.
But I admit this
is exceedingly difficult.
In fact, not even
Lord Beerus has mastered it,
and he's a god.
If you can overcome
the learning curve,
you'll be able to avoid
any danger, however severe.
So, allow me to take
you through every step
of the training required,
in a most meticulous fashion.
In exchange for
delicious foods, of course.
You mean your body reacts
without you having to think?
That's exactly right!
But, uh,
Mister Whis, it looks like
you stepped in some poop.
Ew, ew, ew!
Well my feet do think
for themselves,
but I said nothing
about my shoes.
Anyway, let's get
back to you, Vegeta.
Yeah, what about me?
You are clearly
an extraordinary fighter
on your own. And yet,
for whatever reason,
you're always
one step behind
Goku, am I right?
Oh, you just had to
bring that up didn't you?
Do you know why
you're Goku's lesser?
Please teach me,
oh-wise one.
You walk through life with
a chip on your shoulder,
and your nerves
wound too tight.
This tension makes
it hard for you to move
and fight at your
full potential.
And so, your first
lesson is learning to relax.
When there's a chance
to rest, you must take it.
Like Goku does.
Whis is right.
I do love me a good nap.
But you
have problems, too.
Ooh!
What was that for?
That was a total sucker punch!
Being too relaxed can
also be a weakness.
And don't even
get me started on
the issues with
your overconfidence.
No matter how strong
you are physically,
if you let your focus waver,
you're set up to fail.
I've noticed many
times where you're so sure
of yourself, you let your
guard down in battle.
Huh! He's got that one right.
Well I still think
it was cheap shot.
What is
going on up here?
Some of us are trying
to sleep, you know!
That's one heck of a sneeze!
If we got hit by that,
Whis would be
scraping our bodies
off the ground.
He gets like
this when he's sleepy.
Huh?
Could be worse.
He once plunged this planet
into darkness
when he accidentally
destroyed those two suns.
Wait, if he
blew 'em up,
then how are they
out there now?
Are you guys powerful
enough to make stars?
Of course not. In rare
cases like that one,
I simply perform
a temporal do-over.
And what does that mean?
I reverse time to right
before the incident happens,
and then instead of
letting Beerus do it,
I give him a quick
bop on the noggin.
All right, what the
hell are you? Explain.
Now what's the
best way to explain this?
I'm simply the life form
that's known as Whis!
At the moment, it's my
job to look after Lord Beerus.
As you've no doubt seen,
he has some eccentric manners
and a mighty temper.
So I need certain
skills to cope with him.
- Sounds like the old Destroyer can be...
- Hey! What are you two punch-jockeys
doing up here!
Ee! Oh! Hi, Mister
Lord Beerus, sir.
We asked your
servant Whis to train us.
I figured that much,
I'm not a fool.
What I mean is how
did you two get here?
Don't be mad,
your lordness!
We got in touch
with Mister Whis
and asked him to bring us here!
I can't sense your energy
to find this place so we
had to hitch a ride with him!
It was the only way!
So, Whis brought you here.
Hah! Let me guess.
All it took to
get on your good side
was something high in calories.
Yup! You guessed it.
And why is it so important to
build your strength, Goku?
I hope all this training
isn't your secret way of
gunning for the
job of Destroyer.
Oh, no I'd
never want your job!
All I want is to get stronger!
And I won't let this
clown leave me in the dust,
so I'm training too.
It hadn't dawned on me
'til now just how poorly
you guys get along.
If you ever found a way
to work together for once,
you would be able
to go toe-to-toe
with even Lord Beerus!
No one asked to hear
your opinion, Whis! Can it!
Please. We tried
that once and I'll never
let it happen again.
Vegeta doesn't bug me as
much as I seem to bother him,
but when it comes to fighting,
I work on my own!
Well, I've said my peace.
Hmph. So, what was the price?
What mouth-watering
dish did you bring?
Ah, yes! This time,
a delicacy called, "pizza."
Ooh. What a ridiculous
name for a food!
Is there any left
for me to try,
or did you already
eat it, you swine?
Don't worry, my lord,
I made sure
to save some
leftovers for you!
Excellent!
I shall eat pizza.
But if it's not
absolutely delicious,
I'll destroy you both for
interrupting my slumber,
do you hear me?!
Loud and clear, sir!
I'll heat it up
so it tastes better.
Hold on a minute.
I heard that.
When I asked what
they brought you,
you used the
phrase "This time."
Does that mean you
Earth-huggers have come here
repeatedly
while I was sleeping?
Aah!
What the hell?
They're here!
It feels like they
set down near North City!
Make some room,
you're blocking the view.
Destroying a city is such
a fun way to say, "Hello."
Ah! That cold-blooded monster!
He's gonna pay for this!
Hm?
Heh!
I didn't bring
Chiaotzu or Yamcha.
These guys are too
dangerous for them.
Yeah, Bulma made me promise
I wouldn't say a word
about Frieza's comeback
to Trunks or Goten.
Knowing those two, they'd
challenge him to a duel.
The cavalry has arrived!
Sorry we're
a little bit late.
We figured we should stop
by Korin's place first
to pick up some Senzu Beans.
Wow, Krillin. It's sure
been a while since
I've seen you go full cue ball!
I know! Back in fighting shape.
But let's talk about
you for a moment.
What is going on
with that tracksuit?
Oh, right. Heh.
It all happened so fast,
I had no time to find my gi.
Gohan. Have you kept
up on your martial arts
training at all?
Not really, Master Roshi.
But I can definitely
still turn Super Saiyan
when I want to, maybe!
Is Goku not here yet?
No, but he is coming
soon, you'll see!
Oh look, the little bald one!
I have a distinct memory of
killing him back on Namek.
Ha! Well it seems the
Dragon Balls can resurrect
the powerful and the pathetic.
The Dragon Balls?
So they're the ones
who summoned Shenron.
Well. I'm guessing the
creepy white and purple guy
in the hover pod is Frieza.
Which means
you're a better artist
than I gave you credit for!
Bulma! Why would you
come to ground zero
of Frieza's invasion!
I haven't had any luck
contacting Goku or Vegeta yet,
so I figured I'd be
safer with you guys!
Jaco, get out of
that spaceship
and help my friends
fight these jerks!
Negative! All I said was
that I'd give you a lift.
Oh come on!
You're a galactic patrolman
and there are freaking
aliens invading the planet!
Isn't this your job?
Okay, I'll help.
I'll take on some of
Frieza's soldiers,
preferably the weaker ones.
So who's Mister Spaceman?
Beats me. I'll never
understand how Bulma
has so many weirdo friends.
Hmph.
I thought this might be
a Super Saiyan arriving,
but that symbol is for
the Galactic Patrol.
Hey, creep!
Were the first
two losses not enough?
How'd you come
back to life, anyway?
Hey, stop! You should
be more polite
with guys who can kill you!
Well there aren't many
humans who know who I am,
so I can only assume
you were on Planet Namek
during my battle with
your filthy Saiyan friend?
I'll give you one
final chance to tell me
where that fool Goku is.
You're not just
obsessed with revenge,
you suck at it, too!
What took you so long?
Suffice it to say that I was
tied up for a bit longer
than I would have liked.
Well as stong as Goku's gotten,
he's gonna make your face
look even worse!
If I were you, I'd leave before
I start a fight I can't win!
Stop it, Bulma.
You're not helping!
If I've come all
this way and he no-shows,
I suppose I'll just have to
execute his friends.
The grief that would cause
might be worth the trip.
Gohan, you've gotten a lot
stronger too over the years,
you can handle him, right?
I can handle
his men. I guess.
But this is serious, Bulma.
I don't think you
understand what kind of
opponent Frieza is.
It took my dad
everything he had
to win their battle last time
and Frieza's powered up to
a totally different level.
We can't beat him.
Huh? Oh. Oh crap.
Uh, sorry Mister Lord
Frieza, but Goku is still
on his way back to Earth.
Do you mind waiting
non-violently for
just a little bit longer?
I'll make tea!
I've already spent years
waiting patiently in Hell
for the chance to get
revenge against the Saiyan.
So why not?
I will give Goku another
ten seconds to show.
What? Just ten seconds?
Stingy jerk! Screw you!
Well don't say I didn't
give you a chance.
Soldiers! Give them
everything you've got!
Here they come!
Right! Let's do this!
So by my estimation,
your quota's a hundred
and seventy soldiers each!
That should hold the line
'til Goku and Vegeta get here!
Hm!
Kamehame-Ha!
Oh crap.
Ha!
Hu-ah!
Aah!
Bang!
Hya!
The odds are way
too high against us.
Don't fight in
one place! Spread out!
For a Frieza Force they're
a pretty motley crew,
which works for me!
What the...?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, ow!
Gotta jet!
Tri-beam ha!
Kamehame...
You should learn to
respect your elders!
Eh?
Destructo Disk! Ya!
Got a present for ya!
Huh? Uh-ahhh!
What was that about, freak?
Don't worry,
I didn't forget you.
Hu--aaah!
Ah. That takes a load off.
Say your prayers!
These guys
just don't let up!
Aah!
Hey buddy. Thanks.
That was close.
Sure, you'd do
the same. Right, pal?
Stay here and get some rest.
I'll be right back.
Full force, attack!
Later!
Ya!
Huh?
Whoa!
I don't know you,
but you've got some moves!
The feeling's mutual.
Who are you?
I'm just an Earthling
that knows how to fight!
Really? I thought
you were too strong
and too funny-looking
to be from here.
Huh! Hey!
No. How are they
winning? This can't be!
Oh, this is not
surprising me in the least.
That son of Goku could
wipe out my thousand-man
army in an instant,
if he was so inclined.
Watch him closely and
you'll see his attacks
are deliberately non-lethal.
The boy has a soft heart,
like his father.
Despite all my heinous
provocations on Namek,
Goku still couldn't will
himself to destroy me.
He's a noble man of
great moral clarity.
So pure. It makes
me want to vomit!
Lord Frieza. Sorbet.
Permission to join
in the battle?
Hmm. Good idea.
I'll start with you, Namekian!
Hm.
Special Beam Cannon!
Rest in peace.
- Aah!
- Gotcha!
Aah!
Mm!
Hey Piccolo!
I had him, Gohan!
Maybe so, but let's
not take any chances.
Hmmm.
What the he..?
No. It's not fair!
Not Sasami too!
You'd only seen recordings
of these monkeys in action.
Until you've felt the
heat of a Super Saiyan
staring you down,
you can't possibly
comprehend their power!
Although, I didn't
expect his son to transform.
Here.
- Here, want one?
- No thanks.
It looks like Frieza's
finally ready to fight.
Pathetic. Not that I couldn't
tell the moment I awoke,
but the Frieza Force has
suffered quite the decline.
Eeh.
Please, forgive us.
They're a lot stronger...
than we thought
they'd be, your lordship.
Oh it makes
little difference.
But the aesthetics
is another matter.
I can't stand the sight
of all your anemic,
broken bodies dressed
in my uniforms.
Everyone get back, now!
Jeez. Glad I
don't work for him.
Wow. They're just
as impressive as ever.
But the real threat hasn't
even started fighting yet.
The terror of
Frieza is so legendary,
even the Galactic
Patrol is afraid of him.
Your friends could all
be dead meat, you know.
Telling me that
is not helpful!
What are you doing here anyway?
You should be up there with them!
The more fighters we have
the better our chances!
Oh don't be absurd.
I've already done more than
enough in this fight.
My superiors would never
expect me to challenge
the Evil Emperor himself!
We have a strict policy
against suicide missions.
What do ya think, boys?
If all five of us team up,
do we have a shot against him?
I'm sorry, but no.
He's in a completely
different class than we are,
it's not even close.
Yeah I was thinking the
same thing but I had to ask.
Just wanted to make sure
I wasn't being a chicken.
So the Earth's
valiant defenders
aren't going to advance?
I suppose I'll
have to entertain myself
by killing you, one by one.
I remember when Goku's son
was just a little boy.
It's so touching to see
children grow into their own.
Gohan!
Gohan, wake up!
There we
have it! Not even a
strapping young
Super Saiyan can match
the unstoppable force
of nature I've become.
Come on, stay with me.
Yeah. He's in real trouble.
I think his heart
stopped beating.
He can't swallow a Senzu Bean.
Give me some room!
Down the hatch.
My! That's an
interesting development.
Apparently you Earthlings
have attained a wonder drug.
But how much
time can it buy you?
A few minutes, at best?
Hey. How many more
of those Senzu Beans
do we have, Krillin?
Uh! We've got
one more, that's it.
Ha-ha-haaaa!
Hey, Whis!
You hollered, my lord?
What's this
stuff called again?
The gooey, stretchy
substance on top?
Let's see, what was
it called? Starts with a "C."
It's cheese.
Cheese! Cheese, that's it!
It's a bit pungent
but I love it,
especially when it's all melty!
Aw come on, Lord Beerus.
Do you really have to
interrupt our training
to talk about food?
If I want to, yes.
And I don't recommend
you take that sort of tone
with a Destroyer again.
Don't forget,
your planet's culinary feats
are the only reason
it continues to exist.
But if you prefer,
I can destroy it now
and you can practice in peace.
No, no,
that's okay! I'm sorry.
Ha!
Someone's not
checking his messages!
You got a call from
Earth a while ago,
and I sense it's important!
Uh!
Oh yes, you're right.
It seems I did miss a call.
I wonder if it's another
delectable food offering
from Lady Bulma.
Wouldn't that be nice.
Oh, it is!
And what's she call it?
A strawberry sundae?
I can only hope it tastes
as magnificent as it looks.
Well the girl certainly
has piqued my interest.
I'll just check in
and find out more.
Hurry, I want to know too!
Hello, Lady Bulma?!
This strawberry sundae of yours,
it wouldn't happen to be
a "sweet," would it?
Oh? Is that Whis?
What the hell
took you so long?!
I've been waiting forever!
Vegeta and Goku
are there, right?
Well tell 'em
to come home, now!
And I don't want to hear
any crap about training!
It's an emergency!
That evil scumbag Frieza
has come back to life,
and the Earth's in danger!
Scumbag am I?
- Frieza's back to life?
- Say what?
That can't be true. No way.
After all these years?
Just hold on!
We'll have Whis take us
back as fast as he can!
It takes about thirty-five
minutes at maximum speed.
Are you nuts?
We can't wait that long!
Use your Instant
Transmission, Goku!
This isn't a joke!
Uh, I've gotta sense my
target for it to work, Bulma,
and I'm not sure I can
from this far away.
Frieza's energy
is huge, right?
And the guys will help too!
Hey, Goku's about to
use Instant Transmission
and he needs a clear
signal to lock onto!
Everybody power up to max!
Huh? Okay!
Uh... What are
they doing, my lord?
I'd guess it's a distress
signal to their savior.
I've got it!
Here, Vegeta, let's go!
What? Please.
You're actually asking me
to hold your hand.
Just do it, okay!
You know how Bulma gets!
We've gotta get there
before she says something
to piss off Frieza!
Next stop, Earth!
Ugh!
Oh!
Dad!
Did we make it in time?
Yeah. I mean
it was close, but sure.
You know just once
it might be nice for you
to show up at
the start of the fight.
Yeah, sorry.
The guest of honor
is here at last.
I've been waiting such
a long time for you.
Hm.
I didn't think
I'd see Vegeta here too,
but monkeys do travel in troops.
All that really
matters to me is
I finally get to destroy you.
I thought we were done
with you for good, Frieza.
How did you come back to life?
His lackeys used the
Earth's Dragon Balls.
It was about six months ago.
Isn't that right?
It was poetic,
using Earth's dragon
to save me from Earth's Hell.
Oh, you can't imagine the
depths of my suffering there.
I spent
most of my days strung up
like a damn pupating moth,
trapped over a field of
delicate little flowers
where bands
of angels and fairies
and enchanted
stuffed animals lived!
They played songs
and danced asinine jigs
as if their only care in life
was when they would get
their next warm, fuzzy hug!
Instead of ruling the
Universe with an iron fist,
I was serenaded by teddy bears!
Well don't try
to put that on me, Frieza.
You're the one who came
to Earth looking for a fight.
That's the only reason
Trunks took your life.
I had to come here,
that's what you don't get.
Because I'll never be able
to sleep in this Cosmos
knowing that
I share it with you!
Your death is my
remedy. That's why I've been
training intensively
every day since my return;
to make sure I won't
lose to you again.
Having to put a real
effort into anything
was a first for me, Goku.
I'll make sure
you suffer for that, too.
You're a lot stronger
now than the last time
I saw you, Frieza...
there's no question about that.
But it's been a really long time
and in case you didn't notice,
I've gotten stronger, too.
The first time we
fought I made mistakes
and you caught me off guard.
To ensure that won't
happen I'm going to
take my final form
from the start.
Uh! Holy crap.
That's incredible.
Just what kind of
training did he do?
Guys. This is way
worse than I thought.
If there was ever a time to
run for the hills, this is it.
I'll tell ya this,
you're no pushover,
that's for sure.
If you weren't rotten
to the core, you'd actually
make a perfect
sparring partner for me.
What a waste of talent.
That's just the sort of
small-minded drivel
that makes your
existence so intolerable.
Go on. Channel that
Super Saiyan glow I hate so much.
To be honest, Frieza,
I'm not so sure I need to yet.
Well, well, well.
Our monkey's wearing
even bigger britches now.
That's right.
Fine. The black-haired
Goku's pelt
will look just
as good on my wall.
Hm.
Aah..!
Yaaah!
How's that possible?
Frieza's more
monstrous than ever,
but Goku hasn't
taken a single blow!
I feel like I'm stuck in some
kind of bizarro nightmare.
How can one Earthling
have that much strength?
Well he grew up here,
but he is a Saiyan, you know.
You're obviously joking.
The Saiyans were a
brutal warrior race driven
to extinction...
there can't be one here.
It's true. Actually
my husband's a Saiyan, too.
Two Saiyans?!
Ah, come on!
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
It was my job to keep
this world Saiyan-free.
That would be
way too much paperwork.
Take this!
Aah!
Seriously?
That's all you've got?
- Huh?
- Yeow!
Huh?
Stop! This has
gone on long enough!
You promised me we would
take turns, Kakarot!
Jeez, man! Ow!
I barely got
warmed up, you know!
What? Are you
serious, guys? Really?
Oh...
Well how flattering.
No matter how far a pet strays,
he still knows
who holds his leash.
Your gesture isn't
lost on me, Vegeta.
But stay out of this fight.
I want to crush Goku myself.
There, you see? Let me fight
him just a little longer,
and then we can switch off!
Hm...
Hmph. Damn it.
Hm!
Well this is unexpected.
I knew a great deal of time
had passed since our battle.
And I knew you were
the self-improvement type,
but you've climbed
higher than I thought.
I tried to
warn you, Frieza.
It's fortunate
I trained so hard,
or I might actually be scared.
I knew it.
You've been holding
something back, haven't you?
That's well
deduced for a simpleton.
I've held back just like you.
Then let's both go all in.
No more tricks. No reserves.
Very well, monkeys first.
Sure about that? I don't
want you to get discouraged.
But fine, I'll show you.
They're coming back down.
I can't tell
what they're up to.
What do you think?
So what is this,
Super Saiyan with blue hair dye?
It's a little more
complicated than that.
You don't have the patience
for the full story...
so let's say I got a
taste of something called
Super Saiyan God,
and now I've learned to
tap into that power on my own.
Not bad at all, Goku.
This is just
further vindication.
If I hadn't evolved
to a new level myself,
then this might have proven
rather perilous for me.
I think it's time
you stop talking
and start showing me, Frieza.
His power. It's amazing!
What? Frieza has a new form?
I know gold's a bit gauche,
but I wanted to ensure
you grasped my new position
atop the pecking order.
And for the sake
of your feeble mind,
let's keep the
name simple as well.
We'll call this "Golden Frieza."
Of course,
I hope you've realized
this iteration
has far more to it
than a shimmering new façade.
I noticed. To be honest,
you're more powerful
than I was expecting
as well, Frieza,
and it's definitely got my heart
beating a few ticks faster.
This is going to be
quite the epic battle,
my old nemesis.
Sure as hell
won't be an easy one.
Hey, Vegeta!
So you want to take that
turn right now, or what?
Auh! Don't pawn him
off on me now, Kakarot!
He told us he wanted
to fight you, remember?
Okay, let's give this a shot.
Hm.
Ah!
Good afternoon!
Whis and Lord Beerus!
Are you here to help?
Of course not.
We've come here
for that offering of
"the strawberry sundae."
I trust that you've
brought it with you, Bulma?
Huh? Oh, yeah,
I've still got it.
It's in Jaco's ship.
Does it taste
as good as it looks?
I hope so, since I hate
traveling for nothing.
I'll have to destroy
your planet if it's average.
Look. It's not a
good time for dessert!
Eee! Okay, okay,
I'm getting it now!
Just don't blow us
all up if it's
a little melted,
all right?
Was that too much?
I'm still getting used to this.
Okay, it's all yours.
Oh boy! It looks even more
delicious in person!
Here goes!
Mm-mm-mmm!
Delightful!
This uses that dairy
concoction known as
"ice cream" as
it's base, correct?
Interesting. These red
things look like the brains
of those giant frogs
on Planet Manu.
Oh no, it's some kind of
fruit! That's even better!
It's such a burst of flavor!
Try it, Whis. It's great!
Yes I know.
I've already had one.
This dessert's
simplicity is deceptive.
It's quite good.
Speaking of good,
look at Frieza.
He's clearly gotten stronger.
Yes. Goku is
having trouble with him.
Mmm. Oh, Bulma! What is
this sweet, white substance?
It's not ice cream is it?
Um, no,
that's just whipped cream.
Ah!
Look at Vegeta,
just watching.
The Saiyans would win
if they fought as one.
Yes, if they worked together
they'd clearly be unstoppable,
but they're far
too proud to do that.
You mean too stupid.
You said it, not me.
Hmm.
Damn it. Hate to admit it,
but I'm having some trouble.
You say that like
it isn't obvious.
There's no way
around it, Frieza,
you really are impressive.
It took me years of blood
and sweat to reach this level,
but you've caught
up like it's nothing.
Surely you're not trying
to play on my mercy.
Not even Goku
could be that naïve.
I commend you for
putting up a good struggle.
But I won't stop until
I've had my revenge
and you're in far
too many pieces to count!
Yes. You're so close!
Uh...!
What? Beerus?
That not's polite, Frieza,
you forgot to say "Lord."
Lord Beerus,
that's what I meant!
But, uh, what are
you doing here?
Well I would have
thought that was obvious.
I stopped by to eat this
fantastic sundae.
But--But Lord Beerus,
I came here for vengeance,
are you planning to intervene?
Now why would I
possibly care about that?
You're free to do
as you please, Frieza.
But just do it farther
away from my ice cream.
I don't want to confuse your
combat dust for sprinkles.
Then you seriously
didn't come to stop me?
I just told you
to do as you please.
I'm a Destroyer god.
I'm not here to take sides.
Hold on! You mean you'd
really let Frieza win?
It's not my fight, is it now?
What're you talking about?!
If Frieza wins,
he'll kill us all!
Calm down, Bulma.
As long as you keep supplying me
with fine delicacies like this,
I'll make sure that your
life is spared, at least.
You just stay close to me.
Bulma. Is that actually
Lord Beerus the Destroyer?
Yeah, I told you!
Do you think you can
get a quick picture
of me next to him?
You're more than welcome
to ask him yourself, Jaco.
But don't blame me if
the guy disintegrates you.
Uh, never mind.
Well, then. Want to pick
which limb I take first
or shall I surprise you?
You sure
you want to keep going?
You're better off leaving on a
high note, while you still can.
You just got a new life, and
I'd hate for you to waste it.
You can't think I'd retreat
with victory so close at hand.
What sort of fool
do you think I am?
Kakarot, I'll take
my turn now, if you want.
Aw, come on!
That's not fair!
The only reason you're
volunteering now is 'cause
you see his weakness too!
See my weakness?
This is truly becoming a farce!
I hurl you through
cliff sides and you want to
talk about my weakness?
Fine, I'll play along.
What is my fatal shortcoming?
It's not affecting you yet,
Frieza, but it's about to.
Mmm?
You're too eager for
revenge, that's why you'll fail.
Let me take a wild
guess about your training.
You bolted to Earth
the moment you achieved this
new golden form
of yours, didn't you?
And so what if I did?
What's your point?
Your new form is
burning through more power
than your body can supply.
You should've waited
until you were used to
this form and
knew how to regulate it
before you started
picking fights.
Hm! Is that what you cling to?
Well in that case...
I'll just stop wasting my time
and kill you right now!
Huh?!
Eh!
W-What the...?
Mmm.
Interesting. The Saiyans'
prediction is coming true,
and the tables
are starting to turn.
Did you really think
I wouldn't notice?
That was my strawberry
you so casually devoured.
That's a lie
and you know it!
How many have you had?
I've eaten three.
But I've only
had two of them.
Nice try, my lord, but I
know that you've had four.
There were eight to begin with
and I am capable of math.
You're forgetting something.
I am the diety, Whis.
Eh...
Ka...
me...ha...me...
Ha!
I'll send it back.
Oh yeah!
See? I told you
you'd run out of gas.
Now take my advice
and get out of here.
And live to fight another day.
I'll be here for a rematch
when you're ready, I promise.
Damn you!
Why? Why?
This shouldn't be happening!
I am Lord Frieza!
Huh?
Exemplary
marksmanship, Sorbet.
Uh! Thank you,
I live to serve!
Good thing for contingency
plans, right Goku?
As if I'd allow even
the slightest chance
of losing to you again!
Hmmm...
Goku!
Wake up. Torture's no fun
if I can't hear you scream.
You know, I did try to
warn Goku this might happen.
Clearly a dirty move
by Frieza, but effective.
You have to give him that.
Your obsession
with showing me leniency
borders on the pathological!
You're too strong
for your own good,
it's made you overconfident!
A fearless fool who
insists on second chances
and habitually
lowers his guard.
"Here lies one of the
strongest mortals in the Cosmos,
felled by a common ray gun!"
How pitiful does that feel?
Now you're the one on
the ground facing defeat.
You won the battle
but then you lost the war.
And the dream I clung to
in that damned cocoon
is finally at hand!
Now to pick the
fruit of my labor--
the fruit called revenge!
Ooh, now there's
an interesting thought.
We could make this moment
so much more delectable!
Oh, Vegeta,
come down here for a second!
Wouldn't you like to do it?
I know you despise
this Saiyan underling
for daring to be so uppity.
So I'll let you kill him
to prove you've realized
your folly and re-pledge your
loyalty, like the old days.
Do it and
I'll spare you, at least.
Vegeta, no!
Shut your mouth, woman!
Hey. I really
botched this one, huh?
Whis tried to warn you
and yet here you are.
I guess you always
will be a naïve idiot.
Thanks for the offer,
but I can't.
As annoying as
this bastard can be,
it's our rivalry that keeps
pushing me to get stronger.
I can't afford to kill him.
What if I sweeten the deal?
Take Goku's life
and I'll appoint you
the Supreme Commander
of the entire Frieza Force.
Of course I know at the moment
it only consists of Sorbet,
but we'll rebuild it
stronger than ever!
You would make me
your Supreme Commander?
Is that a real offer?
Should I
take that as a "yes"?
Damn it. Now I may
actually regret this...
Huh...?
But I've already
made my decision.
I'm going to pulverize you
until there's nothing left.
Ah! You dare say that to me?
Use your head. Do you
actually think I would
stay loyal to you
after you blew up the planet
I was destined to rule?
Well, I wonder what the
prince would do if he knew
you authorized Planet Vegeta's
destruction from the start?
Shh! Keep that under wraps!
Get down here, Krillin.
Your buddy Kakarot
needs a Senzu Bean.
He's fading fast.
Okay, I'm coming!
Oh, I don't think so!
What the...?!
He's wasn't kidding.
You're in bad shape.
Good thing that
space cop didn't want his.
Thanks, Vegeta.
You really saved my neck!
Ha! You can thank me by
staying out of this fight
from now on.
I'm finishing this!
Yeah, of course! It's your
turn anyway. Have fun!
Please. If you believe
you can defeat me,
then you're more
delusional than ever!
That's right.
You had no idea, did you?
I've been a Super
Saiyan for years, and now...
I too have the power of a god.
Uh!
You of all people
should know this about me.
But I don't share Kakarot's
taste for forgiveness.
I'm sending you back to Hell.
Ha, ha. Your threats
are as empty as your title.
All hail Vegeta,
prince of no one!
No, this can't be real!
This is not the way this ends!
At least try to face
your death with some honor.
And don't dream of
resurrecting again.
You can all go
to Hell without me!
What?!
Uh-oh. Whis, quickly!
Right!
No. How could
anyone be that evil?
There's nothing left.
He destroyed the Earth!
Vegeta. Trunks. Mom
and Dad. They're all gone.
No. That heartless tyrant.
He couldn't just die. He took
the whole planet with him.
You're wrong.
I'm afraid Frieza
is most likely alive.
Yes, that's correct.
His species is able to
surviving in a vacuum.
Tactically speaking, that was
a pretty ingenious move.
It's not fair.
He took everything!
The Dragon Balls
were destroyed as well,
so we can't even
summon Shenron.
There's no way we can
reverse what Frieza's done.
This is my fault.
Damn! Frieza was
right about me!
I should have finished him
off when I had the chance!
Agreed. Then are you
ready to make this right?
Huh?
You failed to
protect your planet
because of your own leniency.
The only way to
avoid this outcome
is to send Frieza back
to his flower garden.
What? But isn't it
too late for that?
Not quite. I can
turn back time, remember?
But you'll have to move quickly.
Three minutes is as far back
as I'm able to manage.
That do-over thing...
Temporal Do-Over.
You actually paid
attention for once!
No, this can't be real!
This is not the way this ends!
At least try to face
your death with some honor.
And don't even dream
of resurrecting again.
You can all go
to Hell without me!
Frieza!
What? No!
Ha!
Damn you, Goku!
Whew, I guess we're safe now.
Selfish glory-hog!
Do you have any shame?
Hey, just take it easy, Vegeta.
It's not what it looks like.
I can explain, okay?
Oh no, you're not
smooth-talking your way
out of this one, Kakarot!
You told me it was my turn!
It's all right, Vegeta!
Goku just saved you
and the whole world!
You should be thanking him!
What does she mean?
Saved the world from what?
I want answers!
That's right,
we time-traveled.
I was worried
about you, Dad.
...just don't
call me funny-looking, okay?
Well who would have thought?
I'm not sure
I can live this down.
What sort of Destroyer helps
bring a world back to life?
We can't thank you
enough. And don't worry,
you'll get plenty
of food out of this.
We'll throw you a huge feast.
Right after we
track down the Dragon Balls
and put North City
back together, that is.
I look forward to it greatly.
That is the real reason
I turned back time
to save your world, you know.
You sure you don't
want to arrest him?
Manipulating time is
a serious Galactic offense.
Oh, my official response is
that I didn't see anything.
Keep walking. I'm not
going to thank you.
This just means we're even.
Take it easy, I didn't
come to talk about that.
I'm just curious what
you think about Whis saying
if we'd team up in these
battles then people like Frieza
wouldn't even have
the chance to knock us out.
Should we practice
fighting together
in case we need to sometime?
Hmph. I'd rather die
than ever do that again.
Glad to hear it, Vegeta.
I feel the same way!
Hmph. 'Bout time
we agree on something.
Welcome home!
No!
- Yay!
- No!